[
  {
    "title": "1",
    "question": "1",
    "answer": "Seattle Art Museum",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "1",
    "question": "1",
    "answer": "Seattle Public Library",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "1",
    "question": "1",
    "answer": "EMP Museum",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "1",
    "question": "1",
    "answer": "Second & Seneca Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "2",
    "question": "2",
    "answer": "Times Square Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "2",
    "question": "2",
    "answer": "St. Nicholas Russian Orthodox Cathedral",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "2",
    "question": "2",
    "answer": "KeyArena",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "2",
    "question": "2",
    "answer": "Smith Tower",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "3",
    "question": "3",
    "answer": "Cobb Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "3",
    "question": "3",
    "answer": "Seattle Aquarium",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "3",
    "question": "3",
    "answer": "Arctic Club Hotel",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "3",
    "question": "3",
    "answer": "Kolstrand Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "4",
    "question": "4",
    "answer": "Paramount Theatre",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "4",
    "question": "4",
    "answer": "Seattle Tower",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "4",
    "question": "4",
    "answer": "Suzzallo Library",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "4",
    "question": "4",
    "answer": "Harborview Medical Center",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "5",
    "question": "5",
    "answer": "Interurban Building",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "5",
    "question": "5",
    "answer": "Columbia Center",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "5",
    "question": "5",
    "answer": "Pioneer Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "5",
    "question": "5",
    "answer": "Mufasa Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "6",
    "question": "6",
    "answer": "Columbia Center",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "6",
    "question": "6",
    "answer": "1201 Third Avenue",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "6",
    "question": "6",
    "answer": "Speed Stick Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "6",
    "question": "6",
    "answer": "Second and Seneca Building",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "7",
    "question": "7",
    "answer": "Hamilton Middle School",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "7",
    "question": "7",
    "answer": "Union Stables",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "7",
    "question": "7",
    "answer": "California Avenue Substation",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "7",
    "question": "7",
    "answer": "Coliseum Theater Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "8",
    "question": "8",
    "answer": "Dexter Horton Building",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "8",
    "question": "8",
    "answer": "Fairmont Olympic Hotel",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "8",
    "question": "8",
    "answer": "Harborview Medical Center",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "8",
    "question": "8",
    "answer": "KeyArena",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "9",
    "question": "9",
    "answer": "Terminal Sales Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "9",
    "question": "9",
    "answer": "Washington Athletic Club",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "9",
    "question": "9",
    "answer": "Seattle Art Museum",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "9",
    "question": "9",
    "answer": "1201 Third Avenue",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "10",
    "question": "10",
    "answer": "Westin Seattle North Tower",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "10",
    "question": "10",
    "answer": "IBM Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "10",
    "question": "10",
    "answer": "Rainier Tower",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "10",
    "question": "10",
    "answer": "Space Needle",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "11",
    "question": "11",
    "answer": "Decatur Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "11",
    "question": "11",
    "answer": "Alaska Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "11",
    "question": "11",
    "answer": "Cadillac Hotel",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "11",
    "question": "11",
    "answer": "Cobb Building",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "12",
    "question": "12",
    "answer": "Norton Building",
    "correct": "x"
  },
  {
    "title": "12",
    "question": "12",
    "answer": "Westin Building",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "12",
    "question": "12",
    "answer": "Aspira",
    "correct": ""
  },
  {
    "title": "12",
    "question": "12",
    "answer": "Qwest Plaza",
    "correct": ""
  }
]